

# **CALVIN SCRIMSHIRE**

Marketing Professional with Leadership Experience

**661.706.3161** • calvin.scrimshire@gmail.com 929 Paseo Camarillo #692, Camarillo, CA, 93010 www.linkedin.com/in/calvin-scrimshire-69a4b933/

# **EDUCATION & SKILLS**

# Bachelor of Arts, Narrative Storytelling Brooks Institute of Photography, 2008-2011

### **MARKETING**

Google Ads Facebook Ads Taboola Ads AdRoll

### **DESIGN**

Adobe Creative Suite Photo Editing Video Editing Graphic Design

# **WEB DESIGN**

Javascript HTML5 CSS3

### **WEB ENGINEERING**

Design & Test Static Apps CRM System Integration Google Tag Manager Python PHP

## **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

From engaging ads, to thoughtful website improvements, I create allencompassing sales strategies that maximize customer value and increase fiscal revenue.

I'm a Marketing Manager with 7 years experience in e-commerce advertising for high growth brands and outbound lead generation.

Achievements: Grew a brand from \$1m annual sales to \$8m while I was managing their marketing. Also launched a new brand from scratch on Kickstarter earning \$300k, becoming the highest grossing pet product on Kickstarter, up until that time. It's now an international brand with over \$4m in annual sales. I achieved these results with a skeleton team (in many cases no marketing or design support at all). I outlined, designed, wrote, photographed, implemented, and in some cases engineered software to support the campaigns and strategies.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **K9 Ballistics** 2013-Present Head of Marketing

 Started as a web designer and worked up to Head of my department. Grew the company's revenue from \$1m to \$8m per year.

# One Fast Cat 2015-Present Head of Marketing

 Sister brand to K9 Ballistics, I launched the Kickstarter campaign that earned \$300,000 in 60 days. I produced multiple viral videos, and One Fast Cat is now a thriving international brand.

# Marketing Consultant 2017-2018

Brief hiatus from the above companies when I decided to become a private marketing consultant. I worked with over 7 start-ups in this time and launched a profitable ecommerce business.

References available upon request.